triphp.com 2014-04-26

# Privacy Policy - Webmaster Tools and Resources - Triphp

**General policy**  
TriPHP respects your privacy. The information that you provide us with, or that is gathered automatically helps us and third parties to monitor our service and provide you with the services that you have subscribed to. Please bear in mind that any personal information that you submit through [forums](http://forum.triphp.com/ "forums"), letters/emails for publication and the like may be collected by others. If you have any concerns, questions or comments please send an email via[ here](http://forum.triphp.com/misc/contact).

**Email newsletters**  
TriPHP operates email newsletters on its site. These are free to sign up to. What we ask of you is your email address, at times we may ask you for further information, which is used for demographic purposes. We do not give our email lists out to other parties unless you choose to opt in to a scheme whereby third parties may use your details for their own purposes. Our newsletters may contain promotions or advertisements from various businesses or information on other sites or services that we offer. If at any time you wish to un-subscribe from our newsletter you may do so by visiting the site you signed up with and using the un-subscribe facility. You may also email the website editor although it may take a longer time before your email address is removed than with the automatic un-subscribe facility.

**Registration**  
Our site may require you to register with us. This is to allow access to extra services that we provide for you. The information is not used for sending you newsletters or promotions unless stated.

**Third party sites**  
Our site operates with third party sites (such as online shops). We may, on occasion, share non-personal aggregated information to these third parties.

**Cookies**  
We use ‘cookies’ to track advertising information and website usage. On certain sites, or third party sites we may utilise cookies for other purposes such as order tracking in online shops or for targeting advertisements to particular types of visitor.

**Surveys**  
On occasion we may conduct online surveys. This is used to gauge our service, collect demographic information and other information that we may find useful. These surveys are optional. We may share non-personal, aggregated information with third parties.

**Security**  
While we strive to keep the information that you supply directly or indirectly secure please be aware that the Internet is not a fully secure medium.

**Competitions**  
From time to time we operate competitions and promotions. Participation in these is optional. Information submitted may be submitted to third parties, check individual competition rules. You may also be given an option to sign up for a free email newsletter, opting out of this does not disqualify you from a competition.

**Usage of information**  
If requested we may submit your information to local or government authorities.

**Corrections / updates**  
You may unsubscribe from our newsletters using the facilities available on the website you signed up with or by emailing the relevant online editor. If you have any problems please email via the [contact](http://forum.triphp.com/misc/contact "contact") page [here.](http://forum.triphp.com/misc/contact)

**Policy changes**  
By using our site you agree to accept this [privacy policy](http://www.triphp.com/privacy-policy/ "privacy policy") and are aware that our policy may change with time. Any changes to this policy will appear on this web page.

This site uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects and stores anonymous data typically through the use of cookies.

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

If you have not [opted out of third-party ad serving](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94152), the cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) may also be used to serve ads on your site, and should be [disclosed in your privacy policy](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94150) as well.

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we’re unable to suggest specific [privacy policy](http://www.triphp.com/privacy-policy/ "privacy policy") language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:

> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).
